BRADLEY YARROW

SOFTWARE ENGINEER

Phone: +2348118022308, | Email: yarrowbradley@gmail.com | Portfolio: https://mobradl.github.io | Github: https://github.com/mobradl |

LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/bradley-yarrow | Key Programming Languages: Javascript, PHP, Typescript

SUMMARY

I'm a very Passionate Software Engineer with over 4 years' experience currently working as a Full stack Developer building SaaS applications, passionate about bringing excellent experiences to the web. I have strong problem-solving skills and I am always learning, discovering new and efficient ways to deal with new and existing problems. I love coding.

WORK EXPERIENCE

March 2022 - Current

Mid Full Stack Developer

Tsunamio Limited Co, Hong kong

Tsunamio is an IT services and IT Consulting Firm that brings curated talents together and outsource to companies

- Worked on a project for a company called https://spacenextdoor.com (SND) for a month (One month Contract)
- Built a simpler Japanese version of https://spacenextdoor.com using NEXTJS and STRAPI
- Review PR of different team members.
- Project link https://reise-web-stag.spacenextdoor.com

OCTOBER 2021 - February 2022

Software Engineer (Contract)

Maribal, Bucharest, Romania

Maribal is a business software service provider with about 6 products in her suite, serving over 10 client companies. At Maribal, I

- Translate need from product owner to finished products.
- Responsible for maintaining existing Legacy systems
- Set up test factories and seeders and write unit and integration tests.
- Setup CI/CD pipelines for testing and deploying applications on dev servers using Bitbucket Pipelines.
- Continuously collaborate with team members to ensure the application is well documented.
- Taking lead on Project as needed
- Built Features and Managed appointment app https://tommurphyservice.ie
- All Applications were built using Laravel Framework

SEPTEMBER 2019 - SEPTEMBER 2021

Software Developer

Peexoo Technologies, Lagos, Nigeria

Peexoo technologies is a SaaS company for photographers to carry out operations and for users to find suitable photographers (https://peexoo.ai).

 Setup CI/CD pipelines for testing and deploying applications on dev servers using Bitbucket Pipelines.

- Collaborated with team members to ensure the application is well documented.
- Implemented real time monitoring/logging on AWS servers using CloudWatch.
- Participate on development process of REST API using Laravel
- Improved performance and reliability of Database
- Built Findmyface feature using AWS Rekognition and Laravel
- Built Peexoo Lookalike Feature using Laravel and AWS recognition
- Built and managed API for https://peexoo.ai

OTHER PROJECTS

- A SaaS platform https://app.certhub.co (Built using Laravel and Livewire)
- https://gitlab.com/mobrad

EDUCATION Self-Thought

SKILLS

Programming Languages

Javascript, Typescript PHP, Python (Beginner), Java (Beginner)

Frameworks / Libraries

Laravel, Vue.js/Vuex, React/Redux, Nodels.Adonisls, Nextjs

Data Storage and Caching

MySQL, MSSQL Server, MongoDB, PostgreSQL, Redis

Cloud Services and Operations

AWS, Docker, CI/CD (Gitlab CI, Bitbucket Pipelines, Jenkins), Error Tracking and performance monitoring (Sentry)

Version Control

Git

Spoken Languages

English

Others

Linux, PHPUnit, Jest, Laravel Dusk